A smart community decision platform for faster, clearer city operations.
Cities have data, but decisions are slowed by scattered systems and delayed interpretation.
One clean cockpit turns civic signals into explainable, human-approved action.
The dashboard focuses attention on the highest-risk ward instead of overwhelming the viewer.
Ward-level risk scores reveal where response teams should look first.
Actions are ranked by urgency, owner, expected impact, and supporting evidence.
The report view creates a shareable civic brief with sources and next steps.
Dashboard, Risk Map, Actions, Reports, and FAQ guide the complete demo flow.
30 seeded records across complaints, traffic, waste, utilities, environment, actions, and documents.
The right panel answers questions in plain English with confidence, evidence, and citations.
Cloud Run, BigQuery, Gemini, ADK, Vector Search, Looker, Cloud Storage, IAM, and Logging.
The system recommends and explains, but humans approve civic decisions.
Faster insight, better resource allocation, and clearer community response.
CivicMind AI turns scattered civic data into actionable community intelligence.